# ALTHAF M A

- althafmarahman@gmail.com
- +91 7012492250
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/althafmarahman
- https://github.com/althafrahman

### PROFILE

Passionate web developer with 1 year of experience using JavaScript, HTML and CSS to build all aspects of the user experience and user interface for client facing landing pages. specialises in using HTML, CSS, jQuery and PHP to build e-commerce websites.

## **KEY SKILLS**

- Software Development
- Data structure & Algorithms
- Object-Oriented Programming
- Web Development

## SKILLS



## **INTERESTS**

- Gaming
- · Playing Football
- Listening Musics

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### **Dimind Innovations**

Web Developer

Jul 2019 – present | Alwaye, Kerala

- Design and developed web applications.
- Implemented responsive pages using bootstrap and CSS.
- Creating new features and functionalities on e-commerce site using HTML, CSS, jQuery and PHP.
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments.
- Contributed with senior developers to develop ERP web applications.

### **Reubro International**

Internship

Jun 2016 – Jul 2016 | Cochin, Kerala

• Implemented websites using HTML, CSS and jQuery.

### **PROJECTS**

### **Shopping Cart**

Shopping website using React.js

Jun 2020 – Aug 2020

- Developed basic e-commerce website using React.js, Redux, JavaScript, JSX and CSS3.
- Extensively used React.js components, React-router and Reactredux concepts.
- Developed reusable react components.

### **Hugs & Kisses**

Build an online kids clothing shopping website

Nov 2019 - Jan 2020

- Worked as a productive and positive team member to design and develop the website.
- Integrated 3rd party APIs like Google-client API and Facebook-Graph API.

### **EDUCATION**

### **B.Tech - Computer Science**

Ilahia College of Enginnering & Technology Jun 2015 – Jun 2019 | Muvattupuzha, Kerala

### **Higher Secondary - Computer Science**

GOVT. H. S. S

Jun 2013 – Jun 2015 | Alwaye, Kerala